Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 5=
(Miss Yu is locked up because of me.)
(I must do something.)
Mother.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
Nowhere?
You think I don't know
what's on your mind?
Are you going to free Miss Yu?
Mother.
How do you know?
You're my son.
Every move of yours
tells me what you're up to.
Nothing escapes me.
Mother.
Please let go of Miss Yu.
I promised the City Lord
to send her back safe and sound.
But you even
locked him up.
Your arm stopped hurting?
And you're playing the saint now?
Mother.
Who told you to lock up Miss Yu?
That person is up to no good.
It's not something
for you to ask about.
And you're not going anywhere.
Stay in your room.
(Shili Pavilion)
Stop struggling. It's pointless.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be suffering
such humiliation here.
You find it funny?
You remind me of our childhood days.
Back then,
you didn't despise me like you do now.
Naughty boy.
Don't you dare get up
without permission.
Yunqing, this is all my fault.
I broke that thing by mistake.
I should be the one punished.
Don't cry, Wan.
But you took the lashing.
You could die.
I'm just hurt.
I won't die.
If I'd known
you'd fall for
another man so easily now,
I shouldn't have
covered for you back then.
Mu Yunqing, why do you care who I like
if you don't want me?
Also,
why do you care to save me?
Song Qiming is not the one for you.
I'm helping you out.
So who is the right one for me?
Who?
Who is it?
You should stay single.
You...
In that case,
let's get divorced.
Stop dawdling.
Stop threatening me with divorce.
Forgot how you refused to leave
the City Lord's Mansion?
That's right, I refused to leave.
But I never asked you to save me.
You stopped me from
investigating...
Investigating what?
None of your business.
If you're truly into Song Qiming,
I'll step aside.
Alright.
I'd love for you to step aside.
Mr. Song is kind and handsome.
And he spends on me.
Unlike someone else
who only makes me mad.
I won't live past thirty
if I stay with you.
Unreasonable.
The City Lord must learn to sweet-talk.
Even City Lord
can't bully our young lady.
Let go.
Calm down.
Move aside.
Enough.
Calm down.
Our City Lord didn't mean it that way.
I admit
our City Lord has some problems.
But they finally
have a chance to talk it out.
If you barge in now,
how can they talk?
What's there to talk about?
You just don't care about our lady.
Step aside now.
Step aside.
I sealed your acupoint.
Once they finish talking,
I'll unseal it.
What did you say?
Cursing me, huh?
Enough. Stop cursing me.
Let's enjoy the show first.
Enough.
We need to find a way out.
I'm the City Lord of Jin City.
Madam Hong wouldn't dare harm us.
Madam Hong dotes on Mr. Song.
You stabbed him.
She won't show mercy.
Are you scared of Madam Hong
or worried you couldn't marry Mr. Song?
What's wrong with you?
You're still obsessing over it?
Focus on something more important,
like how we're getting out.
At critical moments...
I'm on my own.
What are you doing?
No more questions.
Saving you, obviously.
Don't be reckless.
There.
Let me cut the ropes.
With what?
Don't cut me by mistake.
Shut up.
Yu Yingwan, be gentle.
Stop nagging.
Yu Yingwan, go easy.
That hurts.
I know.
Keep it down.
Am I supposed to
listen to something so scandalous?
I can't see.
So I may cut you.
Stop. Come closer.
Keep still.
Hurry.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I scratched my neck. Left side.
(Why did this happen?)
I'm almost reaching it.
Look, I got it.
Brilliant.
Wan, are you alright?
(In the end, I couldn't prevent
what was meant to happen.)
Mu Yunqing, work with me here.
Once you get out,
I'll be able to focus on my mission.
What are you up to?
I'm staying here.
Why are you so determined to stay?
I have things to do.
Give me a few days.
Once I get what I need,
trust me,
I'll go back to you.
Staying here will be
quite inconvenient for you.
It eases my mind to
leave this with you.
(Token)
Don't move, you...
My lord.
My lady, are you fine?
Madam. Emergency.
The City Lord and Miss Yu escaped.
What did you say?
To the City Lord's Mansion.
- Madam.
- Mother.
I'm still here.
Miss Yu.
I've decided to marry Mr. Song.
I'll treat you as my own daughter.
(I must find the mastermind soon.)
You have such great hair.
When I was young,
I had such nice hair, too.
I bet you were
the renowned beauty across the region.
Spare me the flattery.
I'm old now.
This world belongs to your generation.
I sense you mean me no harm.
Could you please tell me
who wishes me ill?
That I cannot disclose.
You could give me some hints.
Does this person covet my position
or the City Lord's?
You're really sharp, young lady.
But such tactics won't work on me.
I'm not revealing anything to you.
Unless
you can keep Qiming happy forever.
You know very well
that the Mobei army repeatedly invades
our borders...
As a woman,
I have no grand ambitions.
I won't support Mu Yunqing.
Nor will I side with Mobei.
I just want a place for my son and me
to live our lives in peace.
If you behave and stay here,
I might tell you a few things.
Otherwise,
I'll hand you over to those people.
Let me toast you with tea
to welcome you into Shili Pavilion.
Madam, what if I change my mind?
Then I shall kill you.
Tomorrow is the fifth day
of the sixth month.
It's an auspicious day.
In my opinion,
it's time to send the divorce papers
to the City Lord's Mansion.
(Madam Hong is omnipotent.
I'll play along for now.)
(In the dream,)
(Eunuch Duan will come to inspect)
(the City Lord's Token tomorrow.)
(Yunqing entrusted it to me
on our wedding night.)
Mobei has long been targeting us.
If the villains obtain
the City Lord's Token,
they will surely collude with Mobei.
Because whoever possesses the token
becomes the legitimate City Lord
and commands Jin City's 30,000 troops.
Everyone
must obey that person without question.
So the token
can mobilize military forces, too?
That's right.
Will you join me
to protect the City Lord's Token
and our people?
Yes, I will.
(Last night, he gave me
the City Lord's Token again.)
(I must find a way to give it back.)
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪